Walter and Naomi Rosenblum Collection of Photography and Photographic History MSS.556
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Walter Rosenblum, 1938-2018; 23.74 Linear Feet in 27 manuscript boxes, 2 half manuscript box, 2 media boxes, 4 flat boxes, 6 oversized flat boxes, and 7 flat file folder
  - Sub-series II.A: Master Prints, 1938-1980; 2 Linear Feet in 2 flat boxes
    - Trees, Goats, Mother, Child (#85) - Haiti, 1958-1959 (Box 70)
    - Skyscape (#84) - Haiti, 1958 (Box 70)
    - Children Selling Flowers (#83) - Haiti, 1958-1959 (Box 70)
    - Block Party (#30) - Pitt St NY, 1940 (Box 70)
    - Smiling Child in Window (#11) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 70)
    - Selling Old Clothes (#3) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 70)
    - Mother and Baby Carriage (#21) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 70)
    - Child on a Swing (#2) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Group in Front of Fence (#1) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Gypsies and Vegetable Dealer (#5) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Three Boys on a Swing (#12) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Girl with Polio (#13) - Rivington St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Flirting (#15) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Man and Dog on Roof (#16) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Boy in Black Coat (#14) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Synagogue (#19) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Moving Man (#17) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Disturbed Woman in Window (#18) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Black Woman in Doorway (#22) - Pitt St NY, 1947 (Box 71)
    - Woman Washing Clothes (#20) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Seated Woman (#10) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Tar Beach (#8) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Young Couple Billiard Parlor (#6) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Gypsy Children Playing Cards (#7) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Chick's Candy Store (#4) - Pitt St NY, 1938 (Box 71)
    - Boy on Roof (#9) - Pitt St NY, 1950 (Box 71)
    - Sister and Brother in Shower Spray (#127) - South Bronx Series, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Couple (#116) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Street Preacher (#122) - South Bronx Series, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Basketball Game (#123) - Mullaly Park, South Bronx Series, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Dance (#124) - Immaculate Conception Senior Citizens Center, Melrose Ave and 152nd St, Bronx NY, South Bronx Series, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Mother and Daughter (#163) - South Bronx, NY, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Family-Waiting Room (#126) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Mother and Child Waiting Room (#125) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, South Bronx Series, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Sick Child (#129) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Street Shower (#130) - Mullaly Park, South Bronx Series, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Blind Basketball Players (#131) - St. Ann's Community Center, South Bronx NY, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Happy Child, Child in Spray (#132) - South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Waiting Room (#134) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, undated (Box 72)
    - Handball Game (#135) - Mullaly Park, South Bronx NY, 1979 (Box 72)
    - We Need Jobs (#136) - South Bronx, NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Mary, Senior Citizens Center (#137) - Toned in Gold, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Boy with Beads (#138) - South Bronx, NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Lovers (#139) - Mullaly Park, South Bronx NY, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Father + Son (#140) - Lincoln Hospital, South Bronx NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Admiring Parade Leader (#133) - South Bronx, NY, 1980 (Box 72)
    - Two Sisters (#128) - Mullaly Park, South Bronx NY, 1979 (Box 72)
    - Pamphili Gardens (#115) - Rome, Italy, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Woman (#114) - Rome, Italy, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Baker (#112) - Rome, Italy, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Horse Show (#111) - Rome, Italy, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Paul Strand (#110) - Orgeval, France, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Cowboys and Indians (#109) - Luxembourg Gardens, Paris France, 1973 (Box 72)
    - Conversation, School Yard (#108) - Rome, Italy, 1973 (Box 72)
    - D Day Rescue (#24) - Omaha Beach, Normandy France, 1944 (Box 72)
    - Untitled (#25) - St, Malo, France, 1944 (Box 72)
    - Funeral (#27) - Colleville-sur-Mer, France, 1944 (Box 72)
    - Reading List of Dead (#31) - Colleville-sur-Mer, France; a few days after D-Day (june), 1944 (Box 72)
    - Prisoners - D Day +1 (#26) - Normandy, France, 1944 (Box 72)
    - Parade (#28) - Pitt St, NYC, 1939 (Box 72)
    - Block Party (#23) - NYC, 1940 (Box 70)
    - Block Party (#29) - Pitt St, NYC, 1940 (Box 70)
    - Boy with Zither (#73) - East Harlem, Series: East Harlem, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Hopscotch (#79) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Three Men (#70) - East Harlem, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Woman in Doorway (#71) - 105 St, NYC, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Boy with Harmonica (#72) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Children in Window, Sisters (#74) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Street Singer (#75) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Boy in Window (#82) - 105 St, NY, 1951 (Box 70)
    - Boy in Window with Guns (#81) - 105 St, NY, 1940 (Box 70)
    - Untitled (#76) - 104th St, New York, undated (Box 70)
    - Child with Basket (#77) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Boy with Folded Arms (#80) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Friends (#78) - 105 St, NY, 1952 (Box 70)
    - Beaching Boat (#63) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Boy in Wooden Tub (#62) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Cleaning Fish (#64) - Gaspe, Canada, 1951 (Box 70)
    - Conversation (#65) - Gaspe, Canada, 1951 (Box 70)
    - Gaspe Horse in Landscape (#66) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Widow (#67) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Fishermen (#68) - Gaspe, Canada, 1951 (Box 70)
    - Shoreline (#69) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Nun with Cross (#61) - Gaspe, Canada, 1949 (Box 70)
    - Group Under Bridge (#119) - Astoria, NY, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Boy with Recruiting Poster (#117) - Long Island City, NY, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Church Communion (#116) - Long Island City, NY, 1975 (Box 70)
  - Sub-series II.B: Exhibition Materials, 1975-2014; 6.63 Linear Feet in 2 manuscript boxes and 4 oversized boxes
    Sub-series II.B contains the traveling exhibit panels from Walter Rosenblum's They Fight With Cameras: Walter Rosenblum in World War II from D-Day to Dachau exhibit, as well as other promotional materials such as invitations, posters, guidebooks, and flyers related to his other exhibitions.
    Materials belonging to the same exhibition(s) were grouped together, when possible.
    - They Fight with Cameras: Walter Rosenblum in WWII from D-Day to Dachau Traveling Exhibition Displays, 2014 (Box 73, Box 74, Box 75, Box Shared Fales 073, Folder 5, Flat-file-folder 21, Flat-file-folder 3, Flat-file-folder 22, Flat-file-folder 2, Flat-file-folder 1)
    - They Fight with Cameras: Walter Rosenblum in WWII from D-Day to Dachau (Companion Book to Exhibition), 2014 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - WR: They Fight with Cameras Show, Manuela, 2014 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - They Fight with Cameras: Walter Rosenblum in WWII from D-Day to Dachau - Traveling Exhibition Mounted Description, 2014 (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
    - Exposicion: Walter Rosenblum Fotografias 1938-1980, 2002 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Wr Exh Lists EU, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - WR/Selected Exhibitions, 1975-1976, 1980, 1988, 1993-1994, 1999, 2005, 2011 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Walter Rosenblum - Russia Exhibition, 2011 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Exhibition Promotional Materials, 1988, 1996-1999, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - WR- Strand BK-Admira, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Changing Chicago - Photographer's Proposal, 1988-1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Strand/Rosenblum Exhibition, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Strand-Rosenblum Roma 2011 Press Clippings, FA_MSS_556_ER_6
    - Documents Relating to Str & Rosenb Exh, 2011 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - WR Exhibition Programs, 1995-1997 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Spanish Refugees Exhibit (In Collaboration with Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archive, ALBA), 2009 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Photographs from the Collection of Naomi and Walter Rosenblum Photography: Art and Artifact, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - "Messages from the Heart" - Photography by Walter Rosenblum, 1996 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Walter Rosenblum: In Search of Pitt Street, 1999 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - "Masters of Photography" Exhibition Poster, undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Walter Rosenblum Exhibition Posters, undated (Flat-file-folder 8)
  - Sub-series II.C: Lecture and Publication Materials, 1944-2018; 1.75 Linear Feet in manuscript boxes
    Sub-series II.C contains Walter's research and lecture notes, as well as some essays and articles he authored.
    - Art Museum Magazines - Articles about Walter Rosenblum, 2013, 2018 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - Writing by Walter Rosenblum, 1963, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 1957 WR Book Proposal (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - WR Lectures, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - "Critical Mass" Article about WR, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Columbia University - Oral History Project, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Printing in B&W (Technique & Lesson Learned), 1993 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Writings - Review of MoMA Exhibition, undated, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Writings by WR, 1949, 1964, 1975-1977 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Teaching, undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - WR/Articles on Lewis Hine, undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Talks by WR, 1952 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Writings by WR (Via Nada - Re: Gomez & Devalle), 1981-1982, 1989, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Interviews with WR, 1991, 1998, 2003-2004 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Lewis Hine Book, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Ballhouse Exhibition/Witkin, NY, undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Weegee Book Review by WR, 1954, 1982, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Pop Photog & Doisneau by WR, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Gaspe, undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Photographing during WWII, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Education of the Young Photographer (WR), 1964, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Hine in Magazine, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Education: Writing & Presentations, Publications, Specifics, Techniques, 1953, 1963, 1970, 1981-1982, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Pop Photog - Article about Boubat, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Writings about WR's (not bio) work, 1950-1951, 1967, 1974-1976, 1991, 1998-1999 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Dr. David Lewis (U of Baltimore) Book Project (not completed), 1981 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - WR/Student Response to South Bronx Work, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - WR/Lectures, 1980-1981, 1984, 1992-1993, 1995, 1998 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Pinney, Melissa AA, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Critical Mass: Response to Walter Rosenblum Lecture, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Ciudad - Walter Rosenblum Doissier de Prensa, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Versilia Oggi (Italian Newspaper), 2005 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Notebook - Meeting with Boubat & Doisneau, 1973 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - "Girl on a Swing" Pitt Street, New York 1938 (essay by WR), undated (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - "Hopscotch" 105th St 1952 (essay by WR), undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - WR Essay about Lewis Hine, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Unitarian Service Committee, 1946-1947 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - "The Education of Picture Minded Photographers - Teaching Photography" (Walter Rosenblum), 1956 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - "5 Weeks with a Camera" (Walter Rosenblum), 1951 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - "The Quiet One: A Milestone" (Walter Rosenblum), 1949 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - WR - Writings on Others, 1977, 1982, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - "Printing in Black and White: Some Thoughts on Printing for the Young Photographer" (Walter Rosenblum), undated (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Articles by WR about PS, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - WR - A Personal Memory of Hine, undated (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Hine - WR Reminiscence, undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Lewis Hine (??) at the International Center for Photography (Walter Rosenblum), undated (Box 80, Folder 18)
- Series III: The Photo League, 1935-2014 (inclusive), 1980-2001 (bulk); 3.31 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes and 1 oversized box
  The Photo League, founded in 1936, was a cooperative of New York based photographers focused on socially conscious photography. Notable members included Walter Rosenblum, Paul Strand, and Lewis Hine. Series III contains copies of the organzation's official publication (Photo Notes), papers related to social justice and the Photo League's mission, materials related to Walter's time as members of the League, exhibition materials related to the Photo League, as well as Naomi and Walter's research notes about the organization.
  - Press Clippings - Re: Photo League, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Paul Strand & The Photo League: A Personal Memoir, 1976 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Photo League Spain/Italy, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - "The Photo League" (Naomi Rosenblum), undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Spain - Photoespana 99, 1999 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Vigano/Spain (Madrid)/PhotoEspana, 1997, 1999, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Photo League Show/Milan, 2000-2001, 2004 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Valladolid, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Photo League Greenberg Gallery Jewish Museum, 2007 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - NYPL/Photo League, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Colombus Museum Photo League Show, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Photo League Women/Spain, 1999-2000 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Pordenone/Liva, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Photo League Show/Venice/Sept-Oct, 1999-2002 (Box 82, Folder 2-3)
  - Dreaming of Tomorrow: Social Documentaries That Moved American Society (in Japanese), 2005 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Mestre/Venice/Vigano/Photo League, undated (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Photo League Works at Queens College, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Chicago/AIC, 2000-2001 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Chicago/After the Crash/1/23/01, undated (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Columbus Museum Photo League, 2001 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Photography American - 1940s/Notes for NR, 1983, 1985, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Photo League Johnson, 1993 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Photo League - NYPL, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Camera as Weapon: Working Photography between the Wars, 1991 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Journal of Homer Folks - Survey Trip for American Red Cross of Civilian Population of European Countries Affected by the War, 1918 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Photo Notes: Official Publication of the Photo League in New York, 1935-1949, 2001 (Box 83, Folder 1-2, Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Museum Exhibit - PL, 2012 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Photo League, 1976, 1983 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - PL - Articles, 1986, 2012 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Materials about Photo League, 1978, 1994, 1998, 2000, 2011, 2014 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Journey to the Cape (Sid Grossman & Millard Lampell), 1959 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Press & Articles about Photo League, 1993, 2000-2001, 2014 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Photo League, 1983, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Photo League, 1936-1951 (College at New Paltz Exhibition), undated (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Article about Photo League - Hadassah Magazine, 2012 (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Magazines with articles about Photo League, 1979, 1983, 2004 (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - NYPL: New York's Photo League, undated (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Photo League, 1938, 1947, 1992, 2001-2003 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Women of the Photo League, 1998 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - "Where Do We Go From Here?" - The Photo League and Its Legacy (1936-2006) (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Rome, Photo League, 2004-2005 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Photo League NYPL - Pinson, undated (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Poster for Ordinary Miracles: The Photo League's New York (film by Nina Rosenblum), undated (Box 93, Folder 8)
- Series IV: Walter and Naomi Rosenblum Personal Materials, 1940-2016 (inclusive), 1980-2005 (bulk); 4.38 Linear Feet in 4 manuscript boxes, 1 flat box, and 3 oversized boxes
  Series IV contains personal items such as the Rosenblums' daily planners, awards, correspondence, address books, postcards, personal photographs, Walter's doctoral degree, materials related to their daughter (Nina), and Naomi's sketchbooks. Some born-digital materials containing photographs are included in this series.
  Materials in this series have been grouped together thematically or by material type, when possible.
  - ACA Publications I - Picasso (Elizabeth McCausland), 1945 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - WR Address Book, circa 1940s (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence w/ Blanche & Milton Brown, 1956, 1959, 1987, 1989, 1992-1993, 1996-1997 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Desk Diary, 1994 (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence with Grace Robertson, 1995-1997, 2000, 2004-2005 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Brooklyn College Magazine, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Random Photographs, undated (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Walter Rosenblum Memorial Invitation, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Walter & Naomi Rosenblum Marriage Certificate (Copy), 1949 (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - 14th Annual Infinity Awards, 1998 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence to Nina Rosenblum about her parents, undated (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Negatives & Positives W&N in China for installation of Hine Exhibition, 1980 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - M. Michelle, M. Mitchell, Y. Masu, M. Malterre, 1978, 1990-2000, 2007-2008, 2011-2015 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Jose Lemoine (Correspondence), 1984-2011 (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - Postcards, 1985, 1987, 1991-1992 (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence to Naomi Re: Walter's Death, 2006 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Horvat, 1986-1987, 1991-1994, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Lash M - Correspondence, 1979, 1984-1986, 2007 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - J. Lemoine, 2000, 2003-2004 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Hancock, 1976-1980, 1982-1985, 1989, 1993, 2000-2001, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Beaufort, 1976-1979, 1982-1983, 1985-1996, 2000 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - France, Italy, 2003 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Naomi Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 1989 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Naomi Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 1993 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Naomi Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 1997-1998 (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Naomi Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 1992 (Box 87, Folder 2-3)
  - Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 1997 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Rosenblum Desk Calendar, 2004 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Berlin International Film Festival (Nina Rosenblum), 1990 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Untitled Sketch, undated (Box 90, Folder 2, Box 93, Folder 7)
  - 16e Festival International de Cinema Nyon Suisse Diplome de Participation decerne a Nina Rosenblum Pour Le Film "America and Lewis Hine", 1984 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - "Director - Nina Rosenblum" Poster, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Council on International Nontheatrical Events Certificate - "Liberators: Fighting on Two Fronts in World War II" (Nina Rosenblum), 1993 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Sketchbooks, undated (Box 90, Folder 12-13, Box 94, Folder 4-7)
  - The Art Comics and Satires of Ad Reinhardt (Thomas B. Hess), 1975 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Walter Rosenblum Doctor of Fine Arts Diploma - University of Maryland, 1986 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Naomi and Walter Rosenblum Silhouettes, 1981 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Diploma for The Black West (Nina Rosenblum) - 39 Semana Internacional de Cine de Valladolid Espana, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - In the Shadow of Liberty: U.S. Human Rights Documentary Film Series Poster (Through the Wire - Nina Rosenblum), undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Italian Nina Rosenblum Posters, 2012-2013 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Photo Metro Newspaper - Interview with Naomi Rosenblum, 1989 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - Rosenblum Calendar, 2005, 2015, 2016 (Box 93, Folder 15-17)
  - Office of the Mayor of New York - Proclamation for "Liberators and Survivors Day", 1992 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - The 10th Jerusalem Film Festival - "Liberators: Fighting on Two Fronts in World War II" (Bill Miles & Nina Rosenblum), 1993 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Rosenblum Address Book, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - "Ode to Walter On His Birthday", 2002 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - Rosenblum Award in Spilimbergo, 2004; FA_MSS_556_ER_3
  - Inauguration in Fondazione Mattota(?) May 15 2009, FA_MSS_556_ER_8